Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
"The Secret of Girls" (Episode 4)
"سر الفتيات" (الحلقة الرابعة)
Let me try.
دعني أحاول.
Try it.
جربها.
It's delicious.
إنه لذيذ.
No matter how delicious it is, you can't eat it for a whole month.
مهما كان لذيذًا، لا يمكنك تناوله لمدة شهر كامل.
If you don't like it, just don't eat it.
إذا كنت لا تحبه فلا تأكله.
Can you cook some food differently?
هل يمكنك طهي بعض الأطعمة بطريقة مختلفة؟
Ask Qiu Bei to cook for you.
اطلب من تشيو باي أن يطبخ لك.
Who is Qiu Bei?
من هو تشيو باي؟
Spill the details.
انشر التفاصيل.
Friend.
صديق.
Classmate.
زميل في الصف.
It's delicious.
إنه لذيذ.
It's still delicious
لا يزال لذيذا
Tomorrow at 12 o'clock.
غدا الساعة 12 ظهرا
Yes.
نعم.
You have to write down clearly when he entered to the inn.
يجب عليك أن تكتب بوضوح متى دخل إلى النزل.
Write when enter to the inn in this part.
اكتب عند دخولك إلى النزل في هذا الجزء.
The day after tomorrow at 12 o'clock.
بعد غد الساعة 12 ظهرا
Is that right?
هل هذا صحيح؟
Well, yes.
حسنا، نعم.
Do you remember?
هل تذكر؟
Okay.
تمام.
Me?
أنا؟
I remember.
انا أتذكر.
Xu Jingxi.
شو جينغشي.
What's up.
ما أخبارك.
Do you want to eat?
هل تريد أن تأكل؟
I'm coming.
أنا قادم.
Can I ask a question?
هل يمكنني أن أسأل سؤالا؟
When you said food is included, you meant instant noodles?
عندما قلت أن الطعام متضمن هل تقصد المعكرونة سريعة التحضير؟
No.
لا.
I only know how to cook noodles.
أنا أعرف فقط كيفية طهي المعكرونة.
Have you finished the gravy?
هل انتهيت من الصلصة؟
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
Is it gross?
هل هو مقزز؟
It's delicious.
إنه لذيذ.
Instant noodles are also delicious
المعكرونة سريعة التحضير لذيذة أيضًا
I like this flavor the most.
أحب هذه النكهة أكثر من غيرها.
So.
لذا.
I can come to the kitchen to cook by myself, right?
أستطيع أن آتي إلى المطبخ لأطبخ بنفسي، أليس كذلك؟
You can cook?
هل تستطيع الطبخ؟
Not really
ليس حقيقيًا
I can stir-fry a few dishes.
أستطيع أن أقوم بقلي بعض الأطباق.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
You can use the kitchen to cook.
يمكنك استخدام المطبخ للطبخ.
Well that's fine.
حسنا هذا جيد.
Tell me what you want to cook.
أخبرني ماذا تريد أن تطبخ.
You will cook for lunch tomorrow.
سوف تقوم بطهي طعام الغداء غدا.
Then I don't need to cook noodles.
إذن لن أحتاج إلى طهي المعكرونة.
OK
نعم
Can I ask another question?
هل يمكنني أن أسأل سؤالا آخر؟
What are you - the Encyclopedia of Questions?
ما أنت - موسوعة الأسئلة؟
I'm just a little curious.
أنا فقط فضولي قليلا.
Didn't Sis Yun say at noon,
ألم تقل الأخت يون في الظهيرة،
that you don't like to be touched?
أنك لا تحب أن يتم لمسك؟
And when you hit your head this morning,
وعندما تضرب رأسك هذا الصباح،
is there something with you...
هل هناك شيء معك...
Are we that close?
هل نحن قريبين لهذه الدرجة؟
Sorry.
آسف.
Hurry up and eat.
اسرع وتناول الطعام.
We have to go out after finishing.
علينا أن نخرج بعد الانتهاء.
What's wrong with you?
ما مشكلتك؟
It's okay, I have a stomachache.
لا بأس، لدي ألم في المعدة.
Let me take a break.
دعني آخذ استراحة.
You're not trying to scam me, are you?
أنت لا تحاول الاحتيال علي، أليس كذلك؟
No.
لا.
You are trying to scam me by saying you have a stomachache from eating instant noodles.
تحاول خداعي بالقول إنك تعاني من آلام في المعدة بسبب تناول المعكرونة سريعة التحضير.
Don't try to trick me.
لا تحاول خداعي.
What's the matter?
ماذا جرى؟
It really hurts?
هل يؤلمك حقا؟
Let's go back.
دعونا نعود.
Can you walk?
هل تستطيع المشي؟
You hold my arm.
أنت تمسك بذراعي.
Be gentle.
كن لطيفا.
Is it very painful?
هل هو مؤلم جداً؟
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
Thank you for your help.
شكرا لك على مساعدتك.
It's an old problem of mine.
إنها مشكلة قديمة بالنسبة لي.
I always have stomachaches.
أنا أعاني دائمًا من آلام في المعدة.
I always have medicine.
لدي دائما الدواء.
I didn't even ask you.
ولم اسألك حتى
You don't have to explain to me.
لا داعي لأن تشرح لي.
I'm not like you.
أنا لست مثلك.
Always full of endless questions.
دائما مليئة بالأسئلة التي لا نهاية لها.
It's called staying curious about the world.
يُطلق عليه اسم "البقاء فضوليًا بشأن العالم".
If everyone only cares about themselves,
إذا كان الجميع يهتمون بأنفسهم فقط،
and aren't interested in anything else,
وليسوا مهتمين بأي شيء آخر،
wouldn't that be boring?
ألا يكون ذلك مملًا؟
Okay, you are curious.
حسنًا، أنت فضولي.
Curiosity killed the cat.
الفضول قتل القطة.
You were taking care of someone else.
لقد كنت تعتني بشخص آخر.
And you lost your phone and ID.
وفقدت هاتفك وبطاقتك الشخصية.
You ended up here stranded, working to earn money.
لقد انتهى بك الأمر هنا تقطعت بك السبل، تعمل لكسب المال.
Taking advantage of the free food and drink.
الاستفادة من الطعام والشراب المجاني.
That's not boring.
هذا ليس مملًا.
If that day you were the one with a stomachache,
لو كنت أنت في ذلك اليوم الذي يعاني من آلام في المعدة،
you would also hope someone can help you.
كنت آمل أيضًا أن يتمكن شخص ما من مساعدتك.
I will come to help you.
سوف آتي لمساعدتك.
When I help people,
عندما أساعد الناس،
I don't feel bored.
لا أشعر بالملل.
Okay.
تمام.
Then you should rest now.
إذن يجب عليك أن ترتاح الآن.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Hey.
يا.
Qiu Bei.
تشيو باي.
I am sorry,
أنا آسف،
I can't go to the bar today.
لا أستطيع الذهاب إلى البار اليوم.
A colleague is not feeling well.
زميل لا يشعر بأنه على ما يرام.
I... I'm a little worried.
أنا... أنا قلق قليلاً.
How come there's a piece of clothing missing?
لماذا هناك قطعة من الملابس مفقودة؟
Good morning, sourpuss.
صباح الخير أيها الشخص العابس.
When did you get up?
متى استيقظت؟
I don't know.
لا أعرف.
I didn't see the time.
لم أرى الوقت.
But I think it's been about an hour since I woke up
لكن أعتقد أنه قد مر حوالي ساعة منذ أن استيقظت
I finished washing the sheets and quilt covers.
انتهيت من غسل الملاءات وأغطية اللحاف.
What time is it now.
ما هو الوقت الآن؟
Six thirty-five.
ستة وخمسة وثلاثون.
Then you really never fail to wake me up at six thirty.
ثم إنك حقًا لا تفشل أبدًا في إيقاظي في الساعة السادسة والنصف.
But after a day of adjusting, I'm pretty much used to it now.
لكن بعد يوم من التكيف، اعتدت على ذلك الآن إلى حد كبير.
It might be my biological clock.
ربما تكون هذه هي ساعتي البيولوجية.
I got uip at around the same time at my old job, around 6.
لقد حصلت على UIP في نفس الوقت تقريبًا في وظيفتي القديمة، حوالي الساعة 6.
I have a backup number on my old phone.
لدي رقم احتياطي على هاتفي القديم.
You can use it first.
يمكنك استخدامه أولاً.
You can set an alarm.
يمكنك ضبط المنبه.
Then you can sleep a few more minutes.
وبعدها يمكنك النوم لبضع دقائق أخرى.
This is for me?
هذا بالنسبة لي؟
Just use it first.
فقط استخدمه أولاً.
You are nice.
أنت لطيف.
But this must be a collector's edition.
ولكن يجب أن تكون هذه طبعة جامع.
Can this crack walnuts?
هل يمكن أن يؤدي هذا إلى تكسير الجوز؟
Give it back if you don't want it.
أعدها إذا كنت لا تريده.
Your stomach doesn't hurt anymore.
لم تعد معدتك تؤلمك بعد الآن.
You're in the mood to joke.
أنت في مزاج للمزاح.
I am not that delicate.
أنا لست حساسة إلى هذه الدرجة.
I'm just an ordinary employee.
أنا مجرد موظف عادي.
When I had my job before, I was so busy that I didn't even have time to eat.
عندما كنت أعمل سابقًا، كنت مشغولًا جدًا لدرجة أنني لم يكن لدي وقت حتى لتناول الطعام.
It's normal for young people nowadays to have some stomach problems.
من الطبيعي أن يعاني الشباب في أيامنا هذه من بعض المشاكل في المعدة.
Fine
بخير
I'll go out and buy breakfast for everyone.
سأخرج وأشتري وجبة الإفطار للجميع.
Perfect timing for a little walk-around.
الوقت المثالي للقيام بجولة صغيرة.
I'll buy the ingredients you'll need to make lunch.
سأشتري المكونات التي ستحتاجها لتحضير الغداء.
What do you want to cook?
ماذا تريد أن تطبخ؟
I am fine with everything.
أنا بخير مع كل شيء.
Buy what you...
اشتري ما تريد...
Buy what the whole group will enjoy.
اشتري ما يستمتع به المجموعة بأكملها.
OK
نعم
Hello.
مرحبًا.
Hello, check out.
مرحبًا، تفضل بالخروج.
OK
نعم
Let me take a look.
دعني ألقي نظرة.
The deposit will be returned to your account later.
سيتم إرجاع الوديعة إلى حسابك لاحقًا.
Thank you for choosing Time Inn.
نشكرك على اختيارك Time Inn.
See you next time.
نراكم في المرة القادمة.
Bye.
الوداع.
Goodbye.
مع السلامة.
Sis Wen Shan.
الأخت ون شان.
You actually went shopping.
لقد ذهبت للتسوق فعلا.
Making food for lunch?
تحضير الطعام للغداء؟
Someone volunteered.
لقد تطوع شخص ما.
What are you looking at?
ماذا تنظر اليه؟
Nothing.
لا شئ.
Sourpuss.
حامض.
Please help me tie this apron.
من فضلك ساعدني في ربط هذا المئزر.
Oil will stain my clothes.
الزيت سوف يلطخ ملابسي.
Tie it on,
ربطه على،
I have oil on my hands.
يوجد زيت على يدي.
Please help me pull out my hair.
من فضلك ساعدني في انتزاع شعري.
Hope I'm not interrupting you two.
آمل أن لا أقاطعكما.